(The two girls came out on LOOΠΔ TV Prequel 6!)
? : I watched that
? : the blurred version LOOΠΔ TV…
'Here she is~ the blurred girl~!'
? : Yeah, that’s me~
Kim Lip : I’ve never even came out on LOOΠΔ TV
? : (Prophecy) Will my face get blurred out again?
(The mysterious girl gets blurred two times in a row...)
(Anyway, the girl who's standing on the right-hand side is Kim Lip!!)
Kim Lip : In that case, your face would get blurred twice.
(She didn't know that she will be the next member...)
Kim Lip : My face will get blurred and then your face will get blurred!!
Kim Lip : Nope! We both have to be on LOOΠΔ TV
Kim Lip : WE CAN DO! I think…
(Congratulations on your debut and releasing from blurring, Kim Lip!)
? : The blurred girls of the month…